you know, what it was he was going over a little bit and he went back and then he did it and then she knocked out the guy
Yes, thank you.
It's a very different style of work.
It's a different style of work.
Okay, thank you.
Thank you.
Yes, thank you.
Awesome.
All the four today's regular meeting of the Miami Special together, the 40th.
We're getting days, day and time.
It's easier than you saw the blast in the course.
Thank you for this day and I thank you for this council that gives her energy to help the city.
I thank you for the city employees that sit you watch over.
I said to be with us in this weather that we all permit to say.
I thank you for your time, Jesus.
Amen.
Thank you.
Have a really fun trip.
in this form.
I am the fourth public infatence.
I'm going to start with the terminal panel for the knobs.
I'm going to introduce the right and the adjacent even in the items.
On the five-Concentration and step is recommending item 6 and 7 which are claims in minutes
for the consent of the agenda.
There are no questions that entertain the motion.
Thank you, Perma.
And second rule of call, please.
question, I pour a stir, Lewis, I should.
On an eight is new business and a new business,
Dean and I.
Staff report during your packet and any questions for staff?
I've got a lot of questions.
Dean, you know, it's a big, it's on the honor of five of them.
They don't scare you from the nearest capital.
Yes, after your actions are last meeting, we've thought that doesn't act right.
And there's definitely that get right over COVID action,
but I think we're going to be going out to build and have some things
to be able to look at in March.
We've got to do them all.
So, you know, everything's not scary.
Good.
Thank you.
Item 10 is trustee community announcements.
Any announcements from the SUA trustees?
I am 11 as a journalist.
We're out amongst the judge.
I'll make those.
And second.
Thank you.
We'll go, please.
Western.
Aye.
Louis, Johnson.
Four, sir.
Four.
Shots.
Aye.
Thank you, everyone.